Finding aid to Office of the President William Allan Neilson files CA.MS.00013
Smith College Archives
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Savage, Howard J., 1917-23 (Box 384, Folder 26)
  - Saw, Ruth Lydia, 1927-28; undated (Box 384, Folder 27)
  - Sawyer, Henry B., 1919-38 (Box 384, Folder 28)
  - Sayre, Paul L., 1923 (Box 384, Folder 29)
  - Sca-Sch (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 384, Folder 30)
  - Scales, Laura (Lord) '01, 1922-34 (Box 384, Folder 31)
  - Scandrett, Richard B., Jr., 1932-39 (Box 384, Folder 32)
  - Schinz, Albert, 1917-35 (Box 384, Folder 33)
  - Sci-Scz (misc), 1917-39; undated (Box 384, Folder 34)
  - Scolari, Margaret, 1929-30 (Box 384, Folder 35)
  - Scott, K. Frances, 1925-37 (Box 384, Folder 36)
  - Scott, Walter, 1917-32 (Box 384, Folder 37-38)
  - Sea-Seg (misc), 1917-38; undated (Box 385, Folder 1)
  - Sebring, Emma Goodeve '89, 1919-38 (Box 385, Folder 2)
  - Seelye, Laurenus Clark, 1921-35; undated (Box 385, Folder 3)
  - Seh-Sez (misc), 1918-41; undated (Box 385, Folder 4)
  - Sha-She (misc), 1917-39; undated (Box 385, Folder 5)
  - Sheffield, Alfred D., 1918-36 (Box 385, Folder 6)
  - Shepard, Odell, 1917-36 (Box 385, Folder 7)
  - Sherman, Charles P., 1932 (Box 385, Folder 8)
  - Shi-Shz (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 385, Folder 9)
  - Shipherd, H. Robinson, 1920-34 (Box 385, Folder 10)
  - Si (misc), 1911-39; undated (Box 385, Folder 11)
  - Sidis, Sarah M., 1923-28 (Box 385, Folder 12)
  - Sikelianos, Eva, 1933-35 (Box 385, Folder 13)
  - Silver, Ruth F., 1919-29 (Box 385, Folder 14)
  - Sitler, Ida, 1919-20 (Box 385, Folder 15)
  - Sk-Sl (misc), 1919-32 (Box 385, Folder 16)
  - Sleeper, Henry Dike, 1918-22; undated (Box 385, Folder 17)
  - Sma-Smith, L. (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 385, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Charles William, 1920-28 (Box 385, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Ella Lauchner, 1918-39 (Box 385, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Frances Grace '93, 1920-36 (Box 385, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Frank Channing, 1931-39 (Box 385, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Fred B., 1918-24 (Box 385, Folder 23)
  - Smith, J. C., 1920-37 (Box 385, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Jeremiah, Jr., 1926-28 (Box 385, Folder 25)
  - Smith, M.-Smy (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 385, Folder 26)
  - Smith, M. Ellwood, 1918-33 (Box 385, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Margaret A. P., 1932 (Box 385, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Mary Byers '08, 1918-34 (Box 385, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Reed, 1921-37 (Box 385, Folder 30)
  - Smith, Robert Seneca, 1919-31 (Box 385, Folder 31)
  - Smyth, Mary Winslow '95, 1921-29 (Box 385, Folder 32)
  - Sn (misc), 1918-38; undated (Box 386, Folder 1)
  - Snow, Louis F., 1918-22; undated (Box 386, Folder 2)
  - So (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 386, Folder 3)
  - Soci-Cosgrave, Gertrude and Giovanna, 1931-32; undated (Box 386, Folder 4)
  - Sommerfeld, Martin, 1935-39 (Box 386, Folder 5)
  - Sp (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 386, Folder 6)
  - Spingarn, Joel E., 1927-32 (Box 386, Folder 7)
  - Squire, Walter, 1921 (Box 386, Folder 8)
  - Sta (misc), 1920-39 (Box 386, Folder 9)
  - Stapleton, Katharine Laurence '32, 1932-39 (Box 386, Folder 10)
  - Starck, Adolf Ludwig Taylor, 1918-20 (Box 386, Folder 11)
  - Ste (misc), 1917-39 (Box 386, Folder 12)
  - Stearns, Harold E., 1921-37 (Box 386, Folder 13)
  - Stein, Gertrude, 1935 (Box 386, Folder 14)
  - Sterne, Jerome K., 1929 (Box 386, Folder 15)
  - Stevenson, George Stanley, 1921-39 (Box 386, Folder 16)
  - Sti-Sto (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 386, Folder 17)
  - Stochholm, Johanne Magdalene, 1929-32 (Box 386, Folder 18)
  - Stoffregen, Elizabeth Augusta '28, 1925-31 (Box 386, Folder 19)
  - Str-Stu (misc), 1917-39 (Box 386, Folder 20)
  - Strong, Beulah, 1920-37; undated (Box 386, Folder 21)
  - Studley, Luella and Robert, 1928-33 (Box 386, Folder 22)
  - Sturm, Marthe, 1926-39 (Box 386, Folder 23)
  - Su-Sz (misc), 1917-39; undated (Box 386, Folder 24)
  - Surrette, Thomas Whitney, 1920-24; undated (Box 386, Folder 25)
  - Sypherd, Wilbur Owen, 1917-27 (Box 386, Folder 26)
  - Ta (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 386, Folder 27)
  - Tannenbaum, Samuel A., 1925-37 (Box 386, Folder 28)
  - Taylor, Grace Adelaide, 1921-22 (Box 386, Folder 29)
  - Taylor, William Sentman, 1928-39 (Box 386, Folder 30)
  - Te (misc), 1918-40 (Box 386, Folder 31)
  - Tead, Ordway, 1919-38 (Box 386, Folder 32)
  - Teagle, Alice (Wright) '04, 1926-39 (Box 386, Folder 33)
  - Temple, Maud E., 1918-24 (Box 386, Folder 34)
  - Tha-Thi (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 386, Folder 35)
  - Thayer, Helen (Rand) '84, 1918-34 (Box 386, Folder 36)
  - Tho-Thu (misc), 1919-39 (Box 387, Folder 1)
  - Thom, Douglas A., 1926-33 (Box 387, Folder 2)
  - Thomas, Charles Swain, 1926-39 (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - Thomas, Felicia Chedsey '33, 1932 (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Thomas, M. Carey, 1922 (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Thomson, James L., 1927-34 (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Thorndike, Ashley Horace, 1917-35 (Box 387, Folder 7)
  - Thorndike, A. Marian (Lowell) '95, 1925-26 (Box 387, Folder 8)
  - Thwing, Charles F., 1918-34 (Box 387, Folder 9)
  - Ti (misc), 1919-39 (Box 387, Folder 10)
  - Tiffany, Charles Howard, 1927 (Box 387, Folder 11)
  - Tildsey, John Lee, 1920-27 (Box 387, Folder 12)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1922-35 (Box 387, Folder 13)
  - Titsworth, Susan Sayre '97, 1922-32; undated (Box 387, Folder 14)
  - To (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 387, Folder 15)
  - Todd, Constance L., 1932-36 (Box 387, Folder 16)
  - Todd, David, 1918-38 (Box 387, Folder 17)
  - Todd, Millicent, undated (Box 387, Folder 18)
  - Townsend, Harvey Gates, 1917-33 (Box 387, Folder 19)
  - Tr (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 387, Folder 20)
  - Trent, Lucia '19, 1917-32 (Box 387, Folder 21)
  - Tryon, Alice B., 1925-28 (Box 387, Folder 22)
  - Tryon, Dwight W., 1923-29 (Box 387, Folder 23)
  - Ts-Tz (misc), 1919-38; undated (Box 387, Folder 24)
  - Tullis, Nellie (Oisen) '13, 1930-37 (Box 387, Folder 25)
  - Turner, Frances Virginia ex '27, 1923-24 (Box 387, Folder 26)
  - Tyler, Henry Mather, 1919-31 (Box 387, Folder 27)
  - U (misc), 1918-35; undated (Box 387, Folder 28)
  - Underhill, Mary, 1921-34 (Box 387, Folder 29)
  - Ustick, William Lee, 1919-24 (Box 387, Folder 30)
  - Utter, Robert Palfrey, 1917-23 (Box 387, Folder 31)
  - Va (misc), 1918-39 (Box 387, Folder 32)
  - Vail, Carleton M., 1928-29 (Box 387, Folder 33)
  - Vail, Derrick T., 1923-24 (Box 387, Folder 34)
  - Valentine, Alan Chester, 1928-39 (Box 387, Folder 35)
  - Valentine, Albertine (Flershem) '97, 1920-39 (Box 387, Folder 36)
  - Van Dusen, Henry P., 1939-40 (Box 387, Folder 37)
  - van Kleeck, Mary Abby '04, 1919-39 (Box 387, Folder 38-40)
  - van Winckle, Cortlandt, 1930-39 (Box 387, Folder 41)
  - Ve-Vi (misc), 1918-39 (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Venizelos, E. K., 1921-22 (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - Vezzetti, Anacleta Candida, 1921-39 (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1920-27 (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Vo-Vz (misc), 1920-39 (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - von Erhardt-Siebold, Erika, 1926-36 (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - von Schulze-Gaevernitz, ?, 1921-32 (Box 388, Folder 7)
  - Vorenkamp, Alphons P. A., 1926-39 (Box 388, Folder 8)
  - Wa-Wak (misc), 1920-39 (Box 388, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth, Dorothy ex '22, 1919 (Box 388, Folder 10)
  - Wakeman, Seth, 1925-39 (Box 388, Folder 11)
  - Wal (misc), 1909-39; undated (Box 388, Folder 12)
  - Wallas, Graham, 1919-23 (Box 388, Folder 13)
  - Walsh, David I., 1919-39 (Box 388, Folder 14)
  - Wam-War (misc), 1919-42; undated (Box 388, Folder 15)
  - Ward, Harry F., 1922-28 (Box 388, Folder 16)
  - Ware, Edith Ellen, 1917-28 (Box 388, Folder 17)
  - Was-Waz (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 388, Folder 18)
  - Washburn, Florence (Lincoln) ex '02, 1931-35 (Box 388, Folder 19)
  - Wassenbergh, Abraham, 1928-29 (Box 388, Folder 20)
  - Watt, James, 1926-36 (Box 388, Folder 21)
  - Wea-Wei (misc), 1918-39 (Box 388, Folder 22)
  - Webster, K. G. T., 1919-28 (Box 388, Folder 23)
  - Weed, Charles F., 1919-32 (Box 388, Folder 24)
  - Wel-Wem (misc), 1919-40 (Box 388, Folder 25)
  - Welch, Roy Dickinson, 1918-38 (Box 388, Folder 26)
  - Wells, Edgar H., 1918-28 (Box 388, Folder 27)
  - Wells, Harry Edward, 1920-37 (Box 388, Folder 28)
  - Wells, John S., 1919 (Box 388, Folder 29)
  - Wells, Marguerite Milton '95, 1917-39 (Box 388, Folder 30-32)
  - Wells, Mary Byrd '97, 1927-39 (Box 388, Folder 33)
  - Wen-Wez (misc), 1919-39 (Box 388, Folder 34)
  - Wendell, Barrett, 1927 (Box 388, Folder 35)
  - Wenley, R. M., 1923-27 (Box 388, Folder 36)
  - Wezel, Adrian Peter, 1930-37 (Box 388, Folder 37)
  - Wh-White (misc), 1916-39 (Box 388, Folder 38)
  - White, Helen Constance, 1919-31 (Box 388, Folder 39)
  - White, Jessie (Carter) '87, 1921-30 (Box 388, Folder 40)
  - White, John Stuart, 1918 (Box 388, Folder 41)
  - White, W. A., 1918-33 (Box 388, Folder 42)
  - White, Wilbert W., 1925-26 (Box 388, Folder 43)
  - Whiti-Why (misc), 1918-38; undated (Box 388, Folder 44)
  - Whitmarsh, Elizabeth Prentiss, 1919-24 (Box 388, Folder 45)
  - Whittem, Margaret Huntington '36, 1936-39 (Box 388, Folder 46)
  - Wi-Wilk (misc), 1920-41; undated (Box 389, Folder 1)
  - Wiggins, Inez Louise '01, 1920 (Box 389, Folder 2)
  - Wild, Laura H., 1928-37 (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Wilder, Charlotte Elizabeth, 1926-34 (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - Wilder, Elizabeth '28 and parents, 1925-35 (Box 389, Folder 5)
  - Wilder, Harris Hawthorne, 1919-40 (Box 389, Folder 6)
  - Wilder, Inez (Whipple), 1926-29 (Box 389, Folder 7)
  - Will (misc), 1918-37 (Box 389, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Clara Belle, 1919-27; undated (Box 389, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Frankwood E., 1922-30 (Box 389, Folder 10)
  - Williams, Helen Isabelle, 1918-22 (Box 389, Folder 11)
  - Williams, James M., 1920-28 (Box 389, Folder 12)
  - Williams, Marjorie, 1929-35 (Box 389, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Mary Ella, 1919-32 (Box 389, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Whiting, 1925-32; undated (Box 389, Folder 15)
  - Wilm-Wiz (misc), 1918-43 (Box 389, Folder 16)
  - Wilson, Martha '95, 1918-28 (Box 389, Folder 17)
  - Wilson, Mira Bigelow '14, 1920-37 (Box 389, Folder 18)
  - Wing, Caroline Roberta '96 and Adeline Flint '98, 1924-1939 (Box 389, Folder 19)
  - Wiltham, Rose Adelaide '95, 1918-32; undated (Box 389, Folder 20)
  - Withington, Robert, 1917-45 (Box 389, Folder 21)
  - Wo (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 389, Folder 22)
  - Wolfs, Marie Leonie '08, 1924-35 (Box 389, Folder 23)
  - Wood, Irving Francis, 1928-34 (Box 389, Folder 24)
  - Wood, Ruth Goulding '98, 1919-39 (Box 389, Folder 25)
  - Woodbridge, Frederick J. E., 1923-28 (Box 389, Folder 26)
  - Woodbridge, Homer E., 1920-28 (Box 389, Folder 27)
  - Woodhouse, Chase (Going), 1918-34 (Box 389, Folder 28)
  - Woodhouse, Edward James, 1919-27 (Box 389, Folder 29)
  - Woodhull, Marianna '87, 1919-26 (Box 389, Folder 30)
  - Woodman, Francis Call, 1917-34 (Box 389, Folder 31)
  - Woods, Norma (Hoblit) '10, 1929-39 (Box 389, Folder 32)
  - Woodward, Katharine Shepherd '85, 1920-30 (Box 389, Folder 33)
  - Woolley, Mary Emma, 1918-35 (Box 389, Folder 34)
  - Wr-Wy (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 389, Folder 35)
  - Wright, Alice Morgan '04, 1923-36 (Box 389, Folder 36)
  - Wright, Frederick Warren, 1918-34 (Box 389, Folder 37)
  - Y (misc), 1917-38; undated (Box 389, Folder 38)
  - Young, Kimball, 1923-31 (Box 389, Folder 39)
  - Young, Ruth Elizabeth, 1925-36 (Box 389, Folder 40)
  - Z (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 389, Folder 41)
  - Zinsser, Dorothy (Douglas) '13, 1927-39; undated (Box 389, Folder 42)
- Series II. Organizations
  - A (misc), 1919-38; undated (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Agnes Scott College, 1924-28 (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Alumnae Association, 1920-45; undated (Box 390, Folder 3-4)
  - Alumnae Association: Alumnae College, 1933-38 (Box 390, Folder 5-10)
  - Alumnae Association: Alumnae Council, 1922-39; undated (Box 390, Folder 11)
  - Alumnae Association: Alumnae Fund, 1918-45 (Box 390, Folder 12-13)
  - Alumnae Association: Alumnae House, 1929-38; undated (Box 390, Folder 14)
  - Alumnae Association: Class of 1919 Life Insurance Memorial Fund, 1919-20; undated (Box 390, Folder 15)
  - Alumnae Association Committee on Resources, 1938-39 (Box 390, Folder 16)
  - Alumnae Association-Financial, 1921-45 (Box 390, Folder 17)
  - Alumnae Association-Letter to Alumnae, 1928 (Box 390, Folder 18)
  - Alumnae Association-Letter to Alumnae Responses, 1928 (Box 390, Folder 19-22)
  - Alumnae Association-Register, 1918-30 (Box 390, Folder 23)
  - Alumnae Association: Semi-centennial (1931), 1929-31 (Box 390, Folder 24)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith Alumnae Quarterly, 1925-30; undated (Box 390, Folder 25)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Clubs A-L(misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 390, Folder 26)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Boston, 1921-39 (Box 390, Folder 27)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Brooklyn, 1926-30 (Box 390, Folder 28)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Clubs of California, 1928-39 (Box 390, Folder 29)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Chicago, 1918-41 (Box 390, Folder 30)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Cleveland, 1928-36 (Box 390, Folder 31)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Hartford, 1920-45 (Box 390, Folder 32)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Jefferson County, NY, 1919 (Box 390, Folder 33)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Clubs M-Z(misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 390, Folder 34)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Clubs-Midwest Tour, 1918-1919 (Box 390, Folder 35-38)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of New Haven, 1926-27 (Box 390, Folder 39)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Clubs-Newspaper Clippings, 1920-38; undated (Box 391, Folder 1)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of NY, NY, 1926-29 (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of NY, NY, 1930-35 (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of NY, NY, 1936-39; undated (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of NY, NY Alumnae Service Committee, 1934 (Box 391, Folder 5)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Philadelphia, 1920-28 (Box 391, Folder 6)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Rhode Island, 1928-38 (Box 391, Folder 7)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of St. Paul, 1922-29 (Box 391, Folder 8)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Washington D.C., 1925-35 (Box 391, Folder 9)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Club of Westchester County, 1933-34; undated (Box 391, Folder 10)
  - Alumnae Association: Smith College Relief Unit, 1918-26 (Box 391, Folder 11)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1924-39 (Box 391, Folder 12)
  - American Association of University Women, 1922-29 (Box 391, Folder 13)
  - American Association of University Women, 1930-39 (Box 391, Folder 14)
  - American College Bureau, 1923-28 (Box 391, Folder 15)
  - American Council of learned Societies, 1918-31 (Box 391, Folder 16)
  - American Council on Education, 1918-24 (Box 391, Folder 17)
  - American Council on Education, 1925-26 (Box 391, Folder 18)
  - American Council on Education, 1927-30 (Box 391, Folder 19)
  - American Council on Education, 1931-33 (Box 391, Folder 20)
  - American Relief Administration, 1920-29 (Box 391, Folder 21)
  - American-Scandinavian Foundation, 1921-38 (Box 391, Folder 22)
  - American School in Damascus, 1933-38 (Box 391, Folder 23)
  - American School in France of Prehistoric Studies, 1922-23 (Box 391, Folder 24)
  - American Student Union-Anti War Week, 1934-36 (Box 391, Folder 25)
  - American University Women's Paris Club (Reid Hall), 1925-31 (Box 391, Folder 26)
  - Amherst College, 1918-29 (Box 391, Folder 27)
  - Amherst College, 1930-39; undated (Box 391, Folder 28)
  - Association to Aid Scientific Research by Women, 1917-29 (Box 391, Folder 29)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1917-21 (Box 391, Folder 30)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1923-30 (Box 391, Folder 31)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1931-32 (Box 391, Folder 32)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1933-39 (Box 391, Folder 33)
  - B(misc), 1921-39; undated (Box 391, Folder 34)
  - Baldwin School, 1931-37 (Box 391, Folder 35)
  - Barnard College, 1919-41 (Box 391, Folder 36)
  - Bennett School, 1921-39 (Box 391, Folder 37)
  - Boston School of Physical Education, 1924-30 (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Boston University, 1920-35 (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Bowdoin College, 1925-37 (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Bradford Academy, Bradford Junior College, 1925-39 (Box 392, Folder 4)
  - Brown University, 1921-32 (Box 392, Folder 5)
  - Bryn Mawr College, 1920-1940 (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo, N.Y., 1921-36 (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - Bureau of Vocational Information, 1920-22 (Box 392, Folder 8)
  - Bureau of Vocational Information, 1923-24 (Box 392, Folder 9)
  - Bureau of Vocational Information, 1925-27 (Box 392, Folder 10)
  - Mary A. Burnham School, 1921-39 (Box 392, Folder 11)
  - C (misc.), 1920-43; undated (Box 392, Folder 12)
  - California, University of, 1921-36 (Box 392, Folder 13)
  - Cambridge School of Domestic Landscape and Architecture, 1927-42 (Box 392, Folder 14-17)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1930-34 (Box 392, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1920-34 (Box 392, Folder 19-33)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1935-38 (Box 393, Folder 1-15)
  - Miss Chandor's School, 1922-35 (Box 393, Folder 16)
  - Chicago..., 1928-33; undated (Box 393, Folder 17)
  - Chicago, University of, 1925-34 (Box 393, Folder 18)
  - Cite Universitaire, 1927-29 (Box 393, Folder 19)
  - Clarke School for the Deaf, 1920-39; undated (Box 393, Folder 20-25)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1913-22 (Box 393, Folder 26-28)
  - College Entrance Examination Board-Psychological Examination, 1924-25 (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1926-39 (Box 394, Folder 2-4)
  - College des Etats-Unis, Paris, 1921 (Box 394, Folder 5)
  - College of the City of New York, 1929-36 (Box 394, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, 1918-34 (Box 394, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1926-37 (Box 394, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut College, 1918-41 (Box 394, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Bureau for Women Teachers, 1923-36; undated (Box 394, Folder 10-15)
  - Cornell University, 1920-39 (Box 394, Folder 16)
  - Council of Industrial Studies, 1932-48 (Box 394, Folder 17-19)
  - Crescent Crag Community Center, 1924-35 (Box 394, Folder 20)
  - D (misc), 1920-39 (Box 394, Folder 21)
  - Dana Hall School, 1923-31 (Box 394, Folder 22)
  - Dartmouth College, 1919-40 (Box 394, Folder 23)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1927-30 (Box 394, Folder 24)
  - Delaware, the University of, 1924-39 (Box 394, Folder 25)
  - E(misc.), 1921-37 (Box 394, Folder 26)
  - Educational Aid Society, 1929-36 (Box 394, Folder 27)
  - Elmira College, 1924-38 (Box 394, Folder 28)
  - Emma Willard School, 1925-39 (Box 394, Folder 29)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica Inc., 1925-37 (Box 394, Folder 30)
  - F (misc.), 1919-39 (Box 394, Folder 31)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1934-35 (Box 394, Folder 32)
  - Federation Interalliee des Anciens Combattants, 1930-36 (Box 394, Folder 33)
  - Florentine Center, 1926 (Box 394, Folder 34)
  - French Line, 1931-39 (Box 394, Folder 35-36)
  - Frontenex, Geneva, 1929 (Box 394, Folder 37)
  - G (misc.), 1925-43 (Box 395, Folder 1)
  - General Education Board, 1919-35 (Box 395, Folder 2-4)
  - Geneva Summer study Program, 1927-30 (Box 395, Folder 5)
  - Ginling College, 1919-39 (Box 395, Folder 6)
  - Girl's Clubs, 1924-28 (Box 395, Folder 7)
  - Goucher College, 1922-40 (Box 395, Folder 8)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1925-36 (Box 395, Folder 9)
  - H (misc.), 1921-39; undated (Box 395, Folder 10)
  - Miss Hall's School, 1925-32 (Box 395, Folder 11)
  - Hampton Institute, 1920-39 (Box 395, Folder 12-14)
  - Harley School, 1929-31 (Box 395, Folder 15)
  - Hartridge School, 1920-32 (Box 395, Folder 16)
  - Hathaway-Brown School, 1918-38 (Box 395, Folder 17)
  - Haverford College, 1919-28 (Box 395, Folder 18)
  - Head Mistress Association, 1920-30 (Box 395, Folder 19)
  - Heidelberg University, 1925-36 (Box 395, Folder 20)
  - Hollins College, 1925-35 (Box 395, Folder 21)
  - Hotels, 1922-39 (Box 395, Folder 22)
  - Hunter College, 1928-39 (Box 395, Folder 23)
  - Howard Seminary, 1925-34 (Box 395, Folder 24)
  - I - J (misc.), 1917-39; undated (Box 395, Folder 25)
  - Illinois, University of, 1925-31 (Box 395, Folder 26)
  - Institute for the Coordination of Women's Interests, 1918-36 (Box 395, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Historical Research, University of London, 1934-38 (Box 395, Folder 28)
  - Institute of Women's Professional Relations, 1935-38 (Box 395, Folder 29)
  - Institute of International Education, 1919-25 (Box 395, Folder 30-37)
  - Institute of International Education, 1926-39 (Box 396, Folder 1-5)
  - Intercollegiate Conference, 1924 (Box 396, Folder 6)
  - International Federation of Students, 1924-34 (Box 396, Folder 7)
  - International Federation of University Women, 1921-31 (Box 396, Folder 8)
  - International Institute for Girls in Spain, 1918-38 (Box 396, Folder 9-36)
  - International Institute for Girls in Spain, 1938-44 (Box 397, Folder 1-7)
  - International Student Service, 1934 (Box 397, Folder 8)
  - International Student Service-Summer Student Leadership Institute at Campobello, 1941 (Box 397, Folder 9)
  - Italy (misc.), 1926-39 (Box 397, Folder 10)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1920-37 (Box 397, Folder 11)
  - John Price Jones Corporation, 1919-31 (Box 397, Folder 12)
  - K (misc.), 1924-36; undated (Box 397, Folder 13)
  - Kahn Foundation for the Foreign Travel of American Teachers, 1920-36 (Box 397, Folder 14)
  - Knox School, 1921-35 (Box 397, Folder 15)
  - Kobe College, Japan, 1928-34 (Box 397, Folder 16)
  - L (misc.), 1920-39 (Box 397, Folder 17)
  - Lafayette College, 1931-36 (Box 397, Folder 18)
  - Lake Placid Club, 1924-36 (Box 397, Folder 19)
  - J & R Lamb Studios, 1928-34 (Box 397, Folder 20)
  - Lawrence College, 1933-34 (Box 397, Folder 21)
  - League of Women Voters, 1922-32 (Box 397, Folder 22)
  - Lee School, 1927-35 (Box 397, Folder 23)
  - Liberal Arts College Movement, 1930-31 (Box 397, Folder 24)
  - M (misc.), 1917-39; undated (Box 397, Folder 25)
  - Miss Madiera's School, 1922-30 (Box 397, Folder 26)
  - Miss Marot's School, 1924-39 (Box 397, Folder 27)
  - Massachusetts (misc.), 1919-39 (Box 397, Folder 28)
  - Massachusetts Department of Education, 1917-36 (Box 397, Folder 29)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1935; undated (Box 397, Folder 30)
  - Massachusetts Library Club, 1934-35 (Box 397, Folder 31)
  - Massachusetts, State College; State University, 1921-39 (Box 397, Folder 32)
  - Master School of Music Association, 1930-38 (Box 397, Folder 33)
  - Masters School, 1926-39 (Box 397, Folder 34)
  - Michigan, University of, 1920-37 (Box 397, Folder 35)
  - Middlebury College, 1925-35 (Box 397, Folder 36)
  - Mills College, 1920-37 (Box 397, Folder 37)
  - Milton Academy, 1928-36 (Box 397, Folder 38)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1921-33 (Box 397, Folder 39)
  - Motion Pictures, 1925-39 (Box 398, Folder 1)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1918-39 (Box 398, Folder 2-4)
  - N (misc.), 1920-42; undated (Box 398, Folder 5)
  - Naples Table Association, 1918-20 (Box 398, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Principals of Schools for Girls, 1922-31 (Box 398, Folder 7)
  - National Education Association, 1921-35 (Box 398, Folder 8)
  - National Student Federation, 1926-30 (Box 398, Folder 9)
  - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1918-37 (Box 398, Folder 10)
  - New York University, 1925-45 (Box 398, Folder 11)
  - Northampton (misc.), 1916-39; undated (Box 398, Folder 12)
  - Northampton- Chamber of Commerce, 1921-32 (Box 398, Folder 13)
  - Northampton Community Chest, 1927-34 (Box 398, Folder 14)
  - Northampton- Hampshire Book Shop, 1918-42 (Box 398, Folder 15)